{
  "numOfQs": 10,
  "title": "Sports Quiz",
  "quizitems": [{
    "questiontext":"Which Australian was selected by the Milwaukee Bucks with the first overall pick in the 2005 National Basketball Association (NBA) Draft?",
    "answertext":"Andrew Bogut",
    "choices":["Mark Bradtke",    
     "Andrew Bogut",
     "Patrick Mills",
     "Luke Schenscher"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"With 15,921 runs, which international cricketer holds the record for the most Test runs?",
    "answertext":"Sachin Tendulkar",
    "choices":["Sachin Tendulkar",    
     "Ricky Ponting",
     "Brian Lara",
     "Viv Richards"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"How many players have won 3 Brownlow medal awards, the highest individual honour in Australian Rules football?",
    "answertext":"4",
    "choices":["1",    
     "2",
     "3",
     "4"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"At 9.58 seconds, Usain Bolt holds the record for the fastest time in the 100 metre sprint, but which sprinter holds the female record with 10.49 seconds?",
    "answertext":"Florence Griffith-Joyner",
    "choices":["Marion Jones",    
     "Shelly-Ann Fraser-Pryce",
     "Florence Griffith-Joyner",
     "Carmelita Jeter"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"U.S Baseball star, Babe Ruth played for the Boston Red Sox, New York Yankees and which other baseball team?",
    "answertext":"Boston Braves",
    "choices":["Boston Braves",    
     "Los Angeles Dodgers",
     "Philadelphia Phillies",
     "Cincinnati Reds"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"Which nation won Gold in women’s hockey at the 2012 London Olympics?",
    "answertext":"Netherlands",
    "choices":["Netherlands",    
     "Great Britain",
     "New Zealand",
     "U.S.A"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"Which golfer won the 2013 Masters Tournament in Augusta, Georgia?",
    "answertext":"Adam Scott",
    "choices":["Rory McIlroy",    
     "Phil Mickelson",
     "Adam Scott",
     "Tiger Woods"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"Which 2 male tennis players have the most Wimbledon singles titles, seven each?",
    "answertext":"Roger Federer and Pete Sampras",
    "choices":["Roger Federer and Andre Agassi",    
     "Roger Federer and Raphael Nadal",
     "Pete Sampras and Andre Agassi",
     "Roger Federer and Pete Sampras"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"Retired Australian thoroughbred racehorse, Black Caviar, was undefeated in how many races?",
    "answertext":"25",
    "choices":["23",    
     "24",
     "25",
     "26"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"Which English Premier League football club supporters traditionally sing the song ‘You'll Never Walk Alone’ before commencement of the match?",
    "answertext":"Liverpool FC",
    "choices":["Chelsea FC",    
     "Manchester United FC",
     "Liverpool FC",
     "Leeds United FC"]
  }]   
}